asianmetal.com 2017-12-12

# Asian Metal--About Us

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Information Collection and Use

#### Asian Metal is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. The nature of our web site means that we will obtain and use certain information on our web site (www.asianmetal.com). We will not however sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways other than that which is fully disclosed in this statement. Asian Metal collects information at several different points on the site. This privacy policy sets out the principles governing our use of your personal information on the site. By using the site you agree to this use. 

### Registration

#### In order to use the site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give certain information (such as company and contact name, business address and email address) and specific areas of interest, (i.e. metals and minerals handled, or services provided). This information is stored in a secure database and used to 1) contact you about the services on the site for which you have expressed an interest, 2) provide you with information, and 3) normal use and improvement of the site. 

### Subscription

#### We may request information from you on our subscription form. Here you must provide contact information (name, billing address) and financial information (credit card number, expiration date, VAT, sales tax information). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers’ orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this personal information is used to get in touch with you.

### Cookies

#### We may use cookies on the site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while on the site. Once you close your internet browser, the cookie is terminated. By accepting cookies from our site, you will remain logged in as you click from page to page. If you reject the cookie, you may still use the site; however, you may be limited in some areas of the site. Some of our business partners also employ cookies on the site (i.e. advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over those cookies.

### Log Files

#### To enable us to monitor and improve the site and analyze trends, we gather certain aggregated information about when you use the site, including details of your operating system, browser version, domain name, IP address, the URL you came from and go to and the parts of the site you visit. IP addresses are not linked to personal information.

### Information Sharing

#### We may share, transfer or disclose certain aggregated demographic information to our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information. We may offer the optional use of a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use your personal information for any secondary purposes. We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names, or other information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purpose of providing these services. If you have subscribed to enter information relating to you in the Directory section on this site, you expressly permit us to post the information contained in your directory entry on the site. 

### Links

#### The site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we, Asian Metal, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Asian Metal. 

### Surveys & Contests

#### From time to time, this site requests information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include personal information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (postal or zipcode, job position). Personal information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the site. 

### Security

#### This site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When you submit sensitive information via the site, your information is protected and encrypted. If you have any questions about the security at the site, you can send an email to info@asianmetal.com. 

#### While we will take all reasonable steps to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information you disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of providing information online and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been negligent or in willful default. 

#### If you feel that Asian Metal is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact Elsa Wang by e-mail: info@asianmetal.com or phone (86 10 59080011/22/33/44).
